Cha Woosol, come to your senses!
Hey, you little shits!
Woosol! Woosol!
This morning, there was a song called
Known by name
The body of a fighter
Found in the Han River
It happened because of a conflict with the manager
It is presumed to be an incident
The manager who killed the awl
By taking one's own life
It is estimated
Among the dead bodies was the lover of the awl
Including Mr. Choi...
Are you awake?
Where are my friends?
Look at this, you're looking for a friend first.
I told you this would happen, didn't I?
Huh, what the heck
Why are you doing this?
I told you I'd see you later
how have you been doing?
Now that I live, I think about it
I think it needs to change
So these days I
I'm building up some knowledge
Where are my friends?
We're talking now
concentration
I said a while ago
It became a currency exchange
So I read books too
I also watched the documentary
Well, then I found out
In Africa
They're sending the kids to war
I don't know about that
My friends, Jihee and Wonjun
Where are you...
Makes kids mentally unstable
They say you can kill someone by shooting them with a gun
In Africa
ruler
Then, let's get those kids in line
How do I let go
After putting on the blindfold
After giving me the gun
Makes you shoot straight ahead
Bang, bang, bang!
On a wall that is clearly empty
I thought you shot a gun
I took off my blindfold
There's a dead person in front of me
I got shot by my own gun
Then what will happen to him?
Are you going to have a mental breakdown?
After that, do as you are told
This is all done
ruler
So now those African kids
Let's try to understand mentality.
If you know, choose
yes?
Choose, who you want to kill.
You have that kind of hair too
It's not that good, is it?
It's simple
If you choose, that person dies
The remaining people are alive
You won't get hurt
huh?
Oh, choose who to save
Isn't that more comfortable?
Because the two have nothing to do with each other
Can't you just send it to me?
Boy, what the hell! That's
I'm not having fun, Woosol
I'm through to the end
I want to be with you
I have a next appointment
Anyway, choose carefully
Fighting, Chawoosol
Oh, wait, wait
No, I'm fine with just me.
Hey there, hey there, just a moment!
Excuse me, do as I say
I said I'll do it all! Yes?
I'll do whatever you say, okay?
- I told you to do whatever you say!
- Oh, leave the recording on.
- Over there, over there!
- yes
If you hold out, I'll just kill you both
Excuse me!
Wait a minute!
Hey, listen to me...
Woosol-ah
fizzle
Oh, look at this kid
Anna, fuck, UV rays
Hey, right
telerecording
Hey, relay room
Ana, shit, I have to go to the shop.
hey
Pick quickly
I'll give you 10 seconds, 10
Oh, wait, wait
- If you don't choose within the time limit
- Oh, wait, wait
Both die
- 9
- Oh, I said I would, I said I would.
I told you to do whatever I tell you.
What should I do?
Will you spare my life? Yes?
Save me?
- 7
- don't do it!
Don't do it, don't do it, Mr. Lee
Don't do it, don't do it!
Hey, you!
Hey, don't touch either of them.
If you touch me, I'll kill you, you punk!
- 6
- I'll kill you! Don't do it!
Woosol!
I was wrong
I was really wrong
I think I lost my mind for a moment
- Please don't do that, please.
- Well, 4
My friends did nothing wrong
What you're telling me to do
Didn't you just say you're all done?
With your mouth
Did you say it clearly?
If you don't choose within 10 seconds
They both die
I don't know
Mom, mom, I don't know
I really don't know, I don't know, I don't know
What should I do, what should I do?
uh
Jihee, what should I do?
Wonjun hyung
What should I do
I really don't know
I really don't know, I don't know, I don't know...
Wonjun hyung
I really don't know what to do
I don't know
- No, no, I didn't choose it!
- Ding!
I didn't choose it!
Don't do it! It wasn't what I chose!
Eww!
no!
Brother, Wonjun!
At this moment
- Remember it clearly
- Ah, no, no, no!
no!
Oh, no!
I see
Sir, are you okay?
Eww
What the fuck
Ugh, ah!
Ha, you remember it well
Wonjun, are you okay?
If you were me, would you be okay with getting stabbed?
Don't worry, I just brushed past you
-What about Teacher Jihee?
- Oh, it's okay.
Bro, is this really okay?
Is Lee Won-jun going to die if he gets hit with this?
Let's get out of here quickly
Oh, ok, punch combination.
It was very neat
Grab it
The piglet that just left
Catch the rest
Catch it quick! Catch it quick!
If I don't catch you, you think I'll lose everything, huh?
- Hey, get up!
- Grab it!
Hey, Mr. Lee!
Cha Woo-sol, hurry up! Mr. Lee
Come to work!
Jihee!
Hurry up, Mr. Lee.
Oh, sir
Hey, Mr.
Hey, you little shits!
Mr. Lee
Chawoosol!
Hey!
- This bitch!
- Eww!
Jihee!
Oh, Jihee, are you okay?
- Woosol, are you okay?
- uh
Let's get out of here, let's get out
Hey, are you okay?
Oh, yeah, get down, get down quickly.
I think it's that building
Huh? Hey, over there
Hey, move quickly!
Take Teacher Jihee and go out first.
I'll buy some time
That's absolutely not possible
Damn it, please listen to me.
Are we all going to die here?
Go in and what?
I'm so sorry
Have you kidnapped anyone?
Oh, shit, that's right, what, like this?
Oh, then sit here
What on earth are we two going to do?
Teacher, I'll see you later.
Jihee, let's go
Because it's hard to make a living
I forgot for a moment
What kind of kid was I originally?
Hit
Oh my
Here it is.
Where are you running off to?
When I signal
Just go up to the light
First of all, definitely go to a place with lots of people
I'm going, okay?
one
two
Huh?
Oh my god, shit
oh my god
See, I'm right?
What are you guys?
What the heck, kid?
Pizza delivery has arrived.
AC, add cheese crust
This chewy guys!
Come on, you little shit
Hey, Woo-sol, what about Won-jun?
You came too late
Don't you think about it, you little shit?
That kid is worth living for.
Sitting there with shit in his mouth
Hyung, where is the car?
Follow us
Hey, bro, bro, come to your senses
Where did you go?
Hey, there it is!
Hey, you little shit!
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up
- Come quickly!
- They're all here.
Woo-sol, come quickly!
Woosol, hurry!
Stop it!
Over there!
- Take my hand!
- Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up
- Hey!
- Catch that kid!
- Bro, no!
- Hyung Won-jun!
- Hey, hey, hey, stop it!
- Catch, block, block
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming
Departure, departure, departure
Seongyong hyung, let's go!
Brother, brother, let's go quickly
Bro, no!
Hey, hey, what's wrong!
Stick to it if you want to die
Fuck, just push it all away.
You little shits
Hey!
Oh my, you fucking retards, shit
Hyung, Hyung, are you okay?
Ah, Seongyong hyung
Go to the hospital quickly.
Brother, just hold on a little longer, Brother
Wait a minute, wait a minute
Hey, hurry up.
Oh, bro, bro, are you okay?
Are you awake?
Woosol-ah
You saw me there earlier
Oh, bro, bro, that's not it
I chose my brother
That's not it, bro
I know, Inma
The kids I was bullying
Look at me like that
Please save me
Please help me
So I know
Lee Wonjun, you little punk
How much is the trauma cost?
If I die before paying it all off
You're really dying
That kid is going to the end
Woosol-ah
this
Instead, I have a favor to ask.
- To these people
- yes?
Please tell me
I'm sorry
Asking someone to apologize
Where are you, bro?
Live and do it yourself, hyung!
that's right
Oh, after all, apples are self-serve
I'm sorry, Woosol.
Never
As trash
Don't die
Hey, brother
- Huh?
- Brother Wonjun?
Brother, brother, no, brother
Brother, brother!
- type
- Brother, Wonjun!
- What should I do?
- Brother Wonjun!
brother!
Brother Wonjun!
No, Wonjun!
Oh my!
Hyung Wonjun!
Wonjun hyung...